Guide to the University Archives Photograph Collection, Glass Negatives and Lantern Slides, circa 1890-circa 1960 UA 023.031 UA 023.031
Special Collections Research Center
- Agriculture, Series 1
  - Fields and Land
    - Field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 102)
    - Field with haystacks and fertilizer - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 103)
    - Field, house, and farm - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 104)
    - Field with haystacks - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 105)
    - Two men in a field with building in the background - Hand Colored Slides, fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 106)
    - Group of men standing in front of a corn field in a hilly area - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 107)
    - Group of people making haystacks - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 108)
    - Velvet beans on corn with a man standing in field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 109)
    - Man and a stack of hay in a hilly region - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 110)
    - Group of men at a class in a field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 111)
    - Group of men in a field in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 112)
    - Group of men in a field in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 113)
    - Group of people in a field on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 114)
    - Group of people in a field (slide is badly cracked) - See broken and cracked slides and negatives 15.115 - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 115)
    - People in a field taking a class in a hilly region - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 116)
    - Two men in a field with bundles of hay - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 117)
    - Woman in a field (see 119) - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 118)
    - Woman in a field (see 118) - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 119)
    - Man in a field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 120)
    - Man in a cornfield - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 121)
    - Two men in a cornfield - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 122)
    - Person on a tractor in a field (slide is cracked) - See broken and cracked slides and negatives 15.123 - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 123)
    - Two people in a field, one is standing, the other is on a tractor - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 124)
    - Walnut trees in a pasture - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 125)
  - Fruit
    - Unidentified (emulsion is cracked an buckled) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 92)
    - Covers on fruit with numbers - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 93)
    - Plants in greenhouse (emulsion is buckled) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 94)
    - Some type of cover for fruit - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 99)
    - Fruit - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 100)
  - Grapes
    - Vitris rotundifolia - suppressed pistil of self fertile seedling of Thomas x Hope - L. R. D. - Instantaneous exposure - projector without ground glass screen - 31 September 1916 (26) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 1)
    - V. rotundifolia - Hope flower bud median section - hermaphrodite flower had June material by L. R. Detzen - photographed with projecting appa. direct current 20" v. low objective magnified 12 diameters - 3 1/4 ges (emulsion is flaking off) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 2)
    - Seed hybrid - (43) 18 December 1918; 1. Vitro rotundifolia (K-19 alpha series 3) on the left; 2. Vitro vinifera (Malaga seedling #1) on the right; 3. Hybrid at bottom. By L. R. D. - Elect. light and gas 3/4' - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 3)
    - V. rotundiflora - Hope flower bred - median section Hermaphrodite flower bred June material photograph with projecting apparatus by L. R. D. magnified 12 diameters 1/4' daylight (emulsion is wearing off) - See Photographs - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 4)
    - Hybrid pollen (25) - 6 June 1919 - Pollen from the Vinifera - Rotundi hybrid vines of [Malaga seedling #1 x (G-52)] Sterile pollen abundant. By courtesy of Z. P. Metcalf - magnified 230 dia. exp. 5" - expose in gas and elect. light 1' - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 25)
    - Hybrid pollen (26) - 6 June 1919 - Pollen from stem [Winchell x (I-1)] hybrid with upright stamens, perfect hermaphroditic - sterile pollen very abundant - magnified 230 dia. 5" exp. L. R. D. by courtesy of Z. P. Metcalf - expose in daylight 10 ft. from window 5," bright day - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 26)
    - Grape - scuppernong trunk - old vine on J. Prenaris Slare - Columbia ? - photo by F. C. R. - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 15)
    - Grape - hybrid - whole vine - dup. 2 (32) - Winchell x light male Rotundifolia - showing character of vine and growth - in dormant stage - photo 27 November 1918, by L. R. D. - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 16)
    - Grape - Scuppernong trunk - old vine on Davenport's place - Columbia, North Carolina - photo F. C. R. (35) dup. - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 17)
    - Grape misk. sn (envelope torn) - pruning, Dec. 1908 - F. C. R. (36) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 18)
    - Grape - Scuppernong trunk - old vine on B. F. Meekin's place - Roanoke, North Carolina - photo F. C. R. dup. - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 19)
    - Grape - Scuppernong - old vine on Roanoke Island - 1908 - F. C. R. (38) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 20)
    - Grape - branch showing (ripped envelope) pollen - Scuppernong fruited half hand pollinated with male pollen - fruitless half left with natural agencies of pollination - photos by F. C. R. (135) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 23)
    - Grape - hybrids - two flower clusters in bud from perfect and from imperfect hermaphroditic vines [Winchell x (alpha - 1)] - the larger cluster bears perfect hermaphroditic flowers with upright stamen while the smaller one bears imperfect hermaphroditic flowers with reflexed stamens - exp. 2" in row 10 ft. from window in daylight, bright day - photo 2 June 1919 - L. R. D. (27) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 26)
    - Grape - V. rotundifolia - dup (29) - bifid tendrils on Scuppernong - photo 17 April 1919 - L. R. D. - gas and elect. light 1 7/4 - 2' - See Photographs - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 27)
    - Scuppernong vine after pruning - C. F. Williams horticulture [1] - See Photographs - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 29)
    - Grapes - Scuppernong vine before pruning - C. F. Williams [2] (negative is broken) - See Photographs and broken/cracked negatives - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 30)
    - [8] unidentified - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 34)
    - Vitis Rotundifolia [10] - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 35)
    - unidentified [11] - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 36)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 181)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 10)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 17)
    - Grapevines and man - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 18)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 19A)
    - Stems - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 20)
    - Grapevine - emulsion is torn and buckled - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 33)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 35)
    - Grapevines - emulsion is cracked and buckled - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 37)
    - Grapevine - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 43)
    - Grapevine - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 44)
    - Grapevines - emulsion is cracked and buckled - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 56)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 57)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 60)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 62)
    - Grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 69)
    - Grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 69B)
    - Group of people picking grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 75)
    - Produce - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 76)
    - Parts of flower - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 79)
    - Stem - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 82)
    - Grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 82A)
    - Grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 13, Envelope 82C)
    - Grapevine (emulsion is buckled) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 84)
    - Grapevine (emulsion is buckled) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 85)
    - Grapevines and boxes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 89)
    - Women picking grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 90)
    - Wall surrounded by trees and plants - grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 102)
    - Grapevine - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 102A)
    - Grapevines (emulsion is cracking and buckling) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 102B)
    - Plant - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 102C)
    - Stems - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 104)
    - Plant stems, possibly grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 105)
    - Grapes - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 106)
    - Grape stems - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 108)
    - Delaware on 1 wire 2 arm renewal - US experiment vineyard - Vineland, NJ - 9-8-12 - 1503 10672 (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 109)
    - Grapevines (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 111)
    - Grapevines (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 112)
    - Grapevines (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 113)
    - Chart of grape names - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 114)
    - Grapevines (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 115)
    - Grapevines (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 116)
    - Two men standing in front of grapevines - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 117)
  - Horses and Mules
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 16)
    - Horse (Cardbox 1, Envelope 17)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 18)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 19)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 20)
    - Horse, unidentified man and two children (Cardbox 1, Envelope 21)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 22)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 23)
    - Horse (Cardbox 1, Envelope 24)
    - Horse and unidentified child (Cardbox 1, Envelope 25)
    - Horse, unidentified child and man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 26)
    - Horse and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 27)
    - (no. 20) Lincoln County, North Carolina - Making Lespedeza hay rake and loader mules - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 18)
    - Horse and mule pulling a plow - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 139)
    - Man with colt and 2 cows in a field (tape is missing from the bottom of the slide) - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 140)
    - Man and horse drawn cart on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 141)
    - Man and horse drawn cart with a light sandy/powdery substance in a hilly field - Shoffner neg. - slide 584A - See 143 - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 142)
    - Man and horse drawn cart in a hilly region - emulsion cracked - See 142 - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 143)
    - Good work stock - man with 2 horses - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 144)
    - Person in a cart pulled by horses in a hilly region - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 145)
    - Animal Science - Horses and Mules - Bringing home the purchase a snap shot - people with horse - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research (Cardbox 13, Envelope 179)
    - A horse, a plow and eleven people. - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 2)
    - A group of four people hooking up a horse and cart at a barn - Hand Colored slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 23)
  - Oxen
    - Man plowing a field with oxen - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 137)
    - People working in a field with a sled pulled by an ox - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 138)
  - Peaches
    - Burning on peach by sales [4] - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 32)
  - Plums
    - Plum - grafts attempted by Getzen 1917 - 25 February 1921 - Milton plum growing - prune dead - bright day, 4PM, stop 1/ 1/3 sec. - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 12, Envelope 13)
    - Plum - original tree at home of W. F. Marshall, Hillcrest St., West Raleigh - #2 time, 1/3 sec. stop 64, bright day, 2PM (19) - 24 February 1921 - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 12, Envelope 14)
    - Plum - 24 February 1921 - Original tree at W. F. Marshall, Hillcrest St., West Raleigh, North Carolina - #1 time 1/5 sec., stop 22, bright day, 2PM - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 12, Envelope 21)
  - Poultry
    - Poorly managed poultry - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 147)
    - Better managed poultry - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 148)
  - Sheep
    - Sheep and unidentified man (emulsion is deteriorating) (Cardbox 1, Envelope 6)
    - Sheep (Cardbox 1, Envelope 7)
    - Sheep (Cardbox 1, Envelope 8)
    - Sheep (Cardbox 1, Envelope 9)
    - Sheep and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 10)
    - Sheep (Cardbox 1, Envelope 11)
    - Sheep and lamb (Cardbox 1, Envelope 12)
    - Sheep and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 13)
    - Sheep and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 14)
    - Sheep and unidentified man (Cardbox 1, Envelope 15)
    - Sheep - 11 June 1914 - Edgecombe County, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 10)
    - Sheep - 1 November 1915 - Ram, Edgecombe County, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 11)
    - Sheep and unidentified man (negative badly chipped in lower left corner) (Cardbox 3, Envelope 17)
    - Sheep provide for other income - sheep, lambs in the hills - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 146)
  - Swine
    - Swine in sty, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 51)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 52)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 53)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 54)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 55)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 56)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 57)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 58)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 59)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 60)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 61)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 62)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 63)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 64)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 65)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 66)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 67)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 68)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 69)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 70)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 71)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 72)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 73)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 74)
    - Swine, Set #13 (Cardbox 3, Envelope 75)
    - General - Hog rack, C. V. Farm - for hauling swine or sheep to market - June 1917, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 1)
    - Swine - 6 July 1916 - Sow, Cruso, North Carolina - Shay's sow, Rosalind, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 12)
    - Swine - 28 May 1921 - P. B. Durocs, Central Farm, Raleigh, North Carolina - main house on central farm occupied by R. S. Curtis - home to right is Geo. Evans (bottom right corner chipped) - See photographs, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 13)
    - Animal Science - Swine (35) - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 1)
    - Animal Science - Swine - Hogs on permanent pasture - farm of D. W. L. Wilkins, Kinston, North Carolina - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 2)
    - Animal Science - Swine - Color slide - Registered Hampshire hogs on a permanent pasture of Dr. Jno. D. Biggs, Williamston, North Carolina - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 3)
    - Animal Science - Swine - Color slide - Duroc Jersey hogs on permanent pasture of R. L. Willoughby, near Arthur, North Carolina (10) - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 4)
    - Agricultural Extension and Research - Farm homes, etc. - Color slide (G-14) - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 5)
    - Swine in a pen - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 149)
    - Swine (negative is broken) (Cardbox 17, Envelope 2)
- Athletics, Series 2
  - Football practice, circa 1916 - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 18)
  - Football team - NCSU Campus (Cardbox 4, Envelope 19)
- Buildings and Structures, Series 3
  - (no. 22) Swain County, North Carolina - Just after a rain - Bryson City - city hall and fire dept. - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 20)
  - House with stone chimney in a hilly area (slide is cracked) - See broken slides and negatives - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 25)
  - House by a stream, probably in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 26)
  - Farm house with Victorian decoration, cars circa 1940 and well - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 27)
  - Farm and farm house - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 28)
  - House, yard and mountain - 4 square type - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 29)
  - House with trees - plantation house - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 30)
  - House - 2 story - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 31)
  - Trench silo filling - several people at a house - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 32)
  - Small house - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 33)
  - House with tobacco hanging on the porch ready for grading - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 34)
  - Stone house surrounded by hills - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 35)
  - House before restoration (see 37) - (slide is cracked) - See broken/cracked slides - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 36)
  - House after restoration (see 36) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 37)
  - Farm house - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 38)
  - House by a stream or river - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 39)
  - House that resembles a train station - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 10, Envelope 40)
  - Unit Demonstration No. 1 - Mountain View Farm - Bill Conley - four people in front of a house - two are holding a lace tablecloth - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 41)
  - Mountain View Farm - Unit Demonstration No. 1 - Bill Conley - two people in front of a sign - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 42)
  - Harold Ken Dale Farm - Unit Test Demonstration Farm - owner W. D. Ketner - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 43)
  - House and lawn (see 45) - (slide has grainy substance on front) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 44)
  - House and lawn (see 44) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 45)
  - Union County house before repairs circa 1930s (see 47) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 46)
  - Union County house after repairs circa 1930s - 1940s (see 46) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 47)
  - House (probably in eastern North Carolina) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 48)
  - Man and woman sitting inside a house in front of a radio. A Progressive Farmer is in the magazine rack and a copy of Diseases and Parasites - Poultry from the U.S. Department of Agriculture is on the floor. The man is reading about poultry raising and the woman is reading a newspaper (see 50 and 51) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 49)
  - Man and woman sitting inside a house in front of a radio looking at a publication. A Progressive Farmer is in the magazine rack and the woman is holding a newspaper (see 49 and 51) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 50)
  - Man and woman standing in cellar full of canned goods (see 49 and 50) - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 51)
  - Boy standing in front of a barn - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 52)
  - Mill shoal/ building council No. 246 Junior Order of UAM - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 53)
  - Church - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 54)
  - Macon County, North Carolina - No. 1 School house, bad ground - Hand Colored Slides, Buildings (Cardbox 11, Envelope 55)
  - House and barn (see 67) - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 68)
  - Barn and farm - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 71)
  - Farm building - probably a chicken house - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 72)
  - Flowers in front of a house in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Various (Cardbox 12, Envelope 154)
  - Stone and wood fence - Hand Colored Slides, Various (Cardbox 12, Envelope 156)
  - Railroad crossing (color slide) - Horticultural science (Cardbox 14, Envelope 110)
  - Agricultural Extension Service - House with stone chimney in a hilly area (slide is cracked) from Box 9 - Hand Colored Lantern Slides - Buildings (Cardbox 15, Envelope 25)
  - Agricultural Extension Service - House - before restoration (see 37) (slide is cracked) from Box 9 - Hand Colored Lantern Slides - Buildings (Cardbox 15, Envelope 36)
- Charts and Graphs, Series 4
  - Color plate - color theory slide - as arranged and made by C. M. Westcott - Buildings and Grounds (Cardbox 4, Envelope 1)
  - Organizational chart - School of Engineering - Engineering Research - Set #18 (Cardbox 5, Envelope 12)
  - Four year undergraduate curricula - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 46)
  - Electrical Engineering Department - 4 year Bachelor's Program - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 47)
  - Electrical Engineering Department - Professional Program (5th year) - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 48)
  - Electrical Engineering Department - Graduate Study - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 49)
  - Supplementary 4-Year Program - B. S. In Construction - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 50)
  - Nuclear Engineering Undergraduate Program - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 51)
  - Engineering Education Work with industry - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 53)
  - Industrial Help to Engineering education - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 54)
  - Graduate Enrollment - Engineering School - 1910-1911 to 1955-1956 - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 56)
  - Graduate enrollment by schools, 1910-1911 to 1955-1966 - Engineering Research, Set #18 (Cardbox 8, Envelope 57)
  - Boring of rifle barrel (tape is wearing off) (Cardbox 8, Envelope 60)